

GOLDIE TIARA

goldietiara.acc@gmail.com

9 081908031969

• https://github.com/goldietiara

Graduate at Dec 22 from Computer Science majoring in Business Information Technology at Bina Nusantara University, I am very confident in my technical abilities and my ability to quickly learn new things, I also have various experience working with design. After trying many fields, I have decided to put all of my effort to became a Front-end engineer for my specialization and future career.

EDUCATION

BINA NUSANTARA UNIVERSITY

Bachelor degree | 2018 - 2022

Business Information Technology - GPA 3.26

WORK EXPERIENCE

INTERNSHIP - CONSULTANT ASSISTANCE

PricewaterhouseCoopers | 3 months | Aug 2022 - Oct 2022

- Application Management Services SAP SF (Resolving client custom request and application issues trough ticketing system).
- Develop training materials for SAP SAC and provide client consultation to enhance working effectiveness and performance.
- Support research and development activities as appropriate.

INTERNSHIP - WEBSITE ASSISTANCE

PricewaterhouseCoopers | 6 months | Jan 2022 - Jul 2022

- Newsletter distribution for Indonesia Infrastructure News.
- Provided technical support for Marketing and Communications Media on the website.
- Designing and revised eye-catching visual content for Digital TV displays.
- Enhanced website and newsletter aesthetics through photo editing.
- Compiled insightful website analytics documentation.

INTERNSHIP - IT SUPPORT

Suntory Garuda Beverages | 11 months | Feb 2021 - Des 2021

- Developed and maintained an automated bug resolution and reporting system for the SGB application.
- Steered 2 application enhancement projects from planning to implementation as a project leader.
- Managed and monthly report master data and shipping transactions.
- Compiled and updated comprehensive IT documentation, including Manuals, SOP, WI, Forms, and Guidelines.

FREELANCE & PART - TIME

FREELANCE - GRAPHIC DESIGNER

PT. Biru Api for Darya Vartia-Laboratoria | 1 months | Jan 2022 - Feb 2022

• Creating visually appealing and impactful content for various social media platforms.

PART-TIME - DESIGN TEAM

Marketing Binus @BEKASI | 10 months | Jan 2021 - Oct 2021

■ Boosting Marketing Efforts through creating visually appealing designs for Social media content, Banners, Flyers, Graphics, Posters, and Event logos.

SKILLS

■ SAP (SuccessFactors - Employee Central, Analytics Cloud, Cloud Integration Platform)	Intermediate
■ Website Analyst (Adobe Experience Manager, Data Visualization)	Intermediate
■ Front-End (React, Next.js, Typescript, Javascript, Tailwind, HTML, CSS, MySQL, Figma, Adobe XD)	Intermediate
UML (Use Case Diagram, Activity Diagram, Sequence Diagram, Class Diagram)	Advanced

■ Microsoft (Word, Excel, Power Point, Virtual Agent, Visio) Advanced

■ Graphic Design (Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Photoshop, Procreate, Affinity Designer, Lumafusion) Advanced

ORGANIZATION AND SOCIAL

STAFF OF CREATIVE DESIGN

Teach for Indonesia Student Community | University Level | 1 Year 3 months | Jan 2020 - Mar 2021

- Volunteering weekly to teaching math and English to children at the Ballarenik Foundation.
- Inspiring and guiding social media content design activists to reach their full potential.
- Overseeing the seamless execution of events through mentorship and supervision of creative design activists.

PUBLICATION AND DOCUMENTATION COMMITTEE

Student Development Innovation in Digital Era Feast by BINUS University | University Level | 1 months | Nov 2019

■ Creating captivating social media content and elevating the event through the creation of engaging motion graphics.

ACTIVIST OF CREATIVE DESIGN

Teach for Indonesia Student Community | University Level | 3 months | Oct 2019 - Dec 2019

- Create eye-catching designs such as posters, banners, certificates and uniforms.
- Volunteering weekly to teaching math and English to children at the Ballarenik Foundation.
- Capturing and documenting event activities at Disability Service and Thisable.
- Serving as secretary and documentation lead for the Blood Donation BINUS @BEKASI in 2019.
- Effectively managing creative design benchmarking projects.

CERTIFICATES

SAP PROFESSIONAL FUNDAMENTALS | Nov 2022

Professional Certificate | Credential ID VGVH7LKCT6CV

- Verify at: https://coursera.org/verify/VGVH7LKCT6CV
- Skills : Client Research and Analysis, Business Transformation, Planning and Project Management, Communication and Engagement.

Understanding the Enterprise Systems Environment | Dec 2022

Professional Certificate | Credential ID S9MUES3RA3G2

- Verify at: https://coursera.org/verify/S9MUES3RA3G2
- : Digital transformation, Intelligent Enterprise, SAP Platform, Business Analysis, Business Process Design.

SAP Customer Engagement and Discovery | Dec 2022

Professional Certificate | Credential ID U8ANSPYLNJCC

- Verify at: https://coursera.org/verify/U8ANSPYLNJCC
- Skills : Managing Workshops, Business Strategic Assessment, Customer Readiness, Customer Engagement and Exploration, Solution Proposal and Communication.

G Google Data Analytics | Feb 2023

Professional Certificate | Credential ID 4445HKFURVTF

- Badge : https://www.credly.com/go/RIYHDpU9
- Verify at: https://coursera.org/verify/professional-cert/4445HKFURVTF
- : Data Aggregation, Data Analytics, Data Calculations, Data Cleaning, Data Ethics, Data Visualization, Presentations, Problem Solving, Spreadsheets, SQL, R, Structured Thinking



